(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Daisuke
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy.
I'm a natural girl,
but you are a prince for me.
Everyday wondering how I become your girl.
Every night I'm feeling your body in my dreams.
I can't sleep at all, hello, morning sun.
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling.
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now
I want you're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love.
daisuke
I'm a natural girl,
but you're prince for me
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy
Everyone wondering how I become your girl
Everynight I'm feeling your body in my dreams,
I can't sleep at all.
Hello morning sun.
My love, my crush, I wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now
I want you're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love.
daisuke
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now
I want you're one for you
Everytime,
everywhere.
I will surely get your honest love.
daisuke
Let's go
One, two, three, let's go
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets, make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
'Til the sun's up
One, two, three, let's go
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
One, two, three, let's go!
Took a bet on love, it's better than I coulda dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh, what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast, only us, make it last
'Til the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated Love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end but we'll
Keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated Love
HiRyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English, Promise!
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? かわいすね！こいつら！
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? They're so cute, aren't they!
やー、頑張ってね。踊って、一緒に踊っていただいたんで、わーい、嬉しい！
Yeah, thank you for working hard and dancing together with me. Yay, I'm so happy!
And, uh, before we, you know, get into all sorts of things. First off, please use the hashtag...
IRySBday2026... Oh, this way.
IRySBday2026! こちらのハッシュタグでぜひ、ぜひツイートしてくださいね、感想など。
IRySBday2026! Please tweet using this hashtag, let me know your thoughts!
If you have anything you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag. These IRySers will definitely get on their phones later on too, to tweet with the hashtag.
And... have you guys noticed something different? なんか、なんかIRySいつもと見た目違うっしょ？
And... have you guys noticed something different? Doesn't IRyS look a bit different from usual?
どう？ レースクイーン！
What do you think? Race queen!
あ、興奮してる。あ、they... they look very excited. Yeah, they're going... they're going mad, yes.
Ah, they're excited. They... they look very excited. Yeah, they're going... they're going mad, yes.
それぐらい、素晴らしいっしょ？ Finally, the race queen outfit is real!
Isn't it wonderful? Finally, the race queen outfit is real!
Yay!
いや、いいね。ありがとうございます。サクラじゃないよ！
Ah, nice. Thank you so much. They're not paid actors!
Alrighty then! Uh, first off though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods!
Yes, here is the line-up this time. Yes, introducing merch pretty early on this time. It's supposed to pop out...
この辺かな？ あ、はい！
Around here? Oh, yes!
グッズは今回こちらになります！
Here are the merch items for this time!
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! あ、言えた。誕生日記念2026！
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026! Ah, I could say it. Birthday Celebration 2026!
Alright, let me introduce the goods one by one. First off, there's this one.
はい、ガイリスも喜んでるね、yes. First up, we have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS (Acrylic Diorama Stand).
Yes, the GuyRyS are happy too. First up, we have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS (Acrylic Diorama Stand).
Diorama StandRyS!
Illustration is by... Very beautiful, huh?
犬乃づぴすけ先生。あ、ちなみにピスケ先生ですね。こちらの衣装もピスケ先生なんですよ。うふふ。
Inu no Zupisuke-sensei! Ah, by the way, it's Pisuke-sensei. This outfit is also by Pisuke-sensei! Hehe.
The diorama stand features IRyS in her Race Queen outfit perfectly...
...capturing the atmosphere of this 3D live stage, yes!
みんなも買おうねー！イェーイ！はい！
Everyone, buy it, okay? Yay! Yes!
And then the second one is this one! Yes!
The ChibiRyS Tote Bag! It's so cute!
Illustration, as in, on the tote bag is by LIEN-sensei!
いつもLIEN先生ありがとう！Thank you so much LIEN all the time! It's so cute, I love ChibiRyS.
Thank you as always, LIEN-sensei! Thank you so much, LIEN, all the time! It's so cute, I love ChibiRyS.
This tote features the mini IRyS in her, um, casual outfit, yes, drawn by LIEN-sensei, so cute!
LIEN先生に描いてもらった、えっと、カジュアルアイリスのね、えっと、ちびになってます。可愛いトート。
It's a cute tote featuring a chibi version of casual IRyS drawn by LIEN-sensei.
ぜひ普段使いしてください。お出かけで使ってね。はい。
Please use it for everyday use. Use it when you go out! Yes!
Please use it when you go shopping and what not. And with the simple design, it's...
...perfect for everyday use. You can pair it with other merch that'll be introducing right after this, so show off your IRyS pride! Yay!
あの、この後に紹介するグッズともね、合わせて使えるんで、楽しみにしててね。はい。
You can pair it with the merch I'll introduce after this, so look forward to it! Yes!
And then the third one...
...is the Race QueenRyS Keychain!
こちらの素晴らしい衣装のキーチェーンになってます。可愛いやろ？
This wonderful outfit has been made into a keychain! Isn't it cute?
あ、欲しいの？ Oh, you guys want it already? They want it already! まだ駄目！
Oh, you want it? Oh, you guys want it already? They want it already! Not yet!
ここからだよ。注文するよね？ You guys are going to buy it, right?
It's from here on out. You're going to order it, right? You guys are going to buy it, right?
Yeah! Yeah! 1セットで終わらないよね？
Yeah! Yeah! You won't stop at just one set, right?
うーん、うーん、もう、爆買いしてくれるそうです！はい！
Hmm, hmm, indeed, they said they'll bulk buy them! Yes!
This is the new plushie featuring my new outfit!
新衣装のアイリスがぬいぐるみのキーホルダーになっちゃったよ。
The new-outfit IRyS has become a plushie keychain!
It's definitely cute on its own, but you can also carry it with its face peeking from the outer pocket of the tote bag!
ぜひトートバッグの中に、ぽんって入れちゃって、一緒にお出かけしてね。
Please put it right inside the tote bag and go out together!
はい！And then the last one is the YabaiRyS Pouch!
Yes! And then the last one is the YabaiRyS Pouch!
みんなの大好きなヤバイリスだよ！何を考えてるんでしょう？
It's everyone's favorite YabaiRyS! I wonder what she's thinking?
I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes!
YabaiRyS is back again! This face pouch with its high-impact design... yes, it's high impact...
...can also be attached to a bag handle!
そう、先ほどね、あの、紹介したトートバッグのね、取っ手にぽんって付けると、とっても可愛いよ！
Yes, if you put it on the handle of the tote bag I introduced earlier, it's super cute!
Yes, you can use it with the tote bag. Just put it on the, on the tote bag, and it'll be a perfect set!
トートとぬい、and the pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world, yes!
Tote, plushie, and the pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world, yes!
あ、ちなみに、this is a pouch, by the way, just clarifying. これはポーチになってます。
Ah, by the way, this is a pouch, by the way, just clarifying. This is a pouch.
So you can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things in it. Yay!
Okay, and then here are the full set bonuses! Yes! The postcard!
Illustration is the same illustration from Pisuke-sensei from the acrylic stand.
犬乃づぴすけ先生の、素晴らしいイラスト。こちらのポストカードでも使ってます。
We are using Inu no Zupisuke-sensei's wonderful illustration for this postcard as well.
The limited edition features a handwritten message, yes...
えーっと、数量限定版は直筆メッセージ、and, uh, foil-stamped duplicate autograph... あ、message... foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message...
Um, the limited edition features a handwritten message, and, uh, foil-stamped duplicate autograph... ah, message... foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message...
ポストカードです！なので、メッセージは直筆、直筆はメッセージの方です。はい。
It's a postcard! So, the message is handwritten... the handwritten part is the message. Yes.
So, you guys are going to buy the limited edition, right? Yeah, yeah. I want you guys to be as hyped as them, yeah!
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message as well!
あの、通常版ももちろんあるんで、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになってます！
The standard version is also available, so it comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message!
So you can get both! ね、あの、限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてねー！イェーイ！
So you can get both! Please get both the limited edition and the standard version! Yay!
みんな可愛いな。You guys are so cute. Aw, aw, they're so cute.
Everyone is so cute. You guys are so cute. Aw, aw, they're so cute.
Look at how big their heads are. 頭でかいね。
Look at how big their heads are. Their heads are huge, aren't they?
あ、挟まれる。あ、痛いよ、痛い、痛いよー。
Ah, I'm getting squeezed! Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
はぁ、はぁ。もう、君たちはしょうがないな。
*panting* Gosh, you guys are hopeless.
There are plenty more announcements coming up! Yeah, if you guys can tell I'm already introducing merch, so...
...there's a lot of other things coming up. このあともね、いろんな大きな告知があるんで...
...there's a lot of other things coming up. There are various big announcements after this too, so...
...ぜひ最後まで見ててくださいね。楽しみにしててね。
...please watch until the end, okay? Look forward to it!
There are still big announcements after this, so stay tuned!
Alright! じゃあ、続きやるぞー！
Alright! Now, let's keep going!
Let's go on with the live! Woo!
ハー！
Ha!
JANE DOE
うう...
Ooh...
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world...
二人だけみたいだね
...it's just the two of us.
なんて少しだけ
I was just, for a moment...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...dreaming a little dream.
その先に月明かり
Beyond that lies the moonlight...
花束の香り
...and the scent of a bouquet,
指に触れる指
and fingers touching fingers.
さよなら　もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I must go now,
何もかも忘れて
forgetting everything.
ガラスの上を　裸足のまま歩く
I walk barefoot on glass,
いたむごとに　血が流れて落ちていく
with every pain, my blood flows and falls.
お願い　その赤い足跡を
Please, follow those red footprints...
辿って　会いに来て
...and come to meet me.
錆びた道路に放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released onto a rusted road,
靴箱の中　隠したリンゴ
and an apple hidden inside a shoe locker.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷は
The scars remaining on your withered skin...
遠い目のように　泳いだ迷子
...are like a distant gaze, swimming like a lost child.
どこにいるの / ここにいるよ
Where are you? / I'm right here.
なにをしてるの / みつめているよ
What are you doing? / I'm watching you.
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side...
遊びに行こうよ
...let's go out and play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を　裸足のまま歩く
I walk barefoot on glass,
いたむごとに　血が流れて落ちていく
with every pain, my blood flows and falls.
お願い　その赤い足跡を
Please, follow those red footprints...
辿って　会いに来て
...and come to meet me.
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world...
二人だけみたいだね
...it's just the two of us.
なんて少しだけ
I was just, for a moment...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...dreaming a little dream.
Gaze on Me!
揺らせ一秒　かけたら Summer girls
Shake it for a second, and we're Summer girls
夢の道は　ストレート
The path of dreams is straight!
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze!
Please Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely about to begin!
(La la la la la)
ゴールは Spot light
Our goal is the spotlight
(La la la la la)
I'm the heroine / (La la la la la)
君を頂戴
Give me all of you!
Please Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely about to begin!
みんな準備はいいですか？ Burning
Is everyone ready? Burning!
うなずいて陽炎も Heat up
Nod along, even the heat haze is heating up!
どうしよう　上昇　明るく...
What should I do? Soaring, brightly...
Let's go! さあ太陽 燃えて最高
Let's go! Come on sun, burn at your best!
Mate
負けられない 興奮もハートも
I can't lose, both my excitement and heart
駆け引きは No no
No bargaining, no no
Gate
開いたなら 一瞬のドラマ
Once it opens, it's a momentary drama
走れ夏の方へ
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら
If you run past even a second...
Summer girls
夢への道は ストレート
The road to our dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと沸き立つ Fantastic
Please, Gaze on Me! It will surely be exciting and fantastic
(La la la la la la)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(The goal is the spotlight)
(La la la la la la)
(I am the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(Give me you)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time)
(It will surely be an exciting, fantastic time)
Oh!
絶対最上 掴みたい
I absolutely want to grasp the very best feeling
Feeling
全身全霊 めぐるから Get heart
My whole body and soul are spinning, so get my heart!
テンション 高揚
Tension rising
欲しいモノへ
Towards what I want
今 Ride
Now, ride...
on time のって It's show time
on time, get on, it's show time
Peak
迎える時 遠慮はいらない
When we reach it, there's no need to hold back
せめぎあい Oh oh
Competing with each other, oh oh
Spark
汗とプライド ジレた運命
Sweat and pride, an impatient destiny
連れて夏の方へ
Take me towards the summer!
挑む世界は 魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world we challenge is the enchanting sunlight floor
天井知らずの ボルテージ
A limitless voltage
火照る季節を モノにして
Make this hot season yours
Please, Gaze on Me! クラリさせたい Exciting time
Please, Gaze on Me! I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time
(La la la la la la)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(The goal is the spotlight)
(La la la la la la)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(Give me you)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(クラリさせたい Exciting time)
(I want to make you dizzy in this exciting time)
関係ない どんな私だって
It doesn't matter who I am
真夏 駆け出せたら Venus
If we run out into midsummer, I'm Venus
アツくなれば 一歩で Change and happy
If we get hot, with one step we change and be happy
(眩しすぎる今日を)
(This today that shines too bright)
踊るように 手にしよう
Let's capture it as if we're dancing
(さあ Here we go!)
(Now, here we go!)
ビートは 止まらない
The beat won't stop!
Keep
思うままに 身を預けて
Surrender yourself just as you please
灼熱へ Go go
To the scorching heat, go go
Warp
本能のリズム 打ち鳴らして
Pound out the rhythm of instinct
走れ夏の方へ
Run towards the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら
If you run past even a second...
Summer girls
夢への道は ストレート
The road to our dreams is straight
視線 誰にも 譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと始まる Fantastic time
Please, Gaze on Me! It will surely begin, a fantastic time
(La la la la la la)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(The goal is the spotlight)
(La la la la la la)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(Give me you)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと始まる Fantastic time)
(It will surely begin, a fantastic time)
Ice cream!
愛♡スクリーム！
Love♡Scream!
Ice cream!
教えて！もっと あなたの事
Tell me! More about you!
Tell me more more more. Tell me more more more.
聞かせて！もっと あなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice!
Let me hear more more more. Let me hear more more more.
こんなドキドキ もう抑えきれない
This pounding heart, I can no longer control it
(All I need you, oh! All I need you.)
(All I need is you, oh! All I need is you.)
友達は卒業
Graduating from being friends
運命の私
I am your destiny
見つけて欲しいの
I want you to find me
One! 勇気を出して
One! Gather your courage
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! Operation: Staring at you
Three! 瞳と目が合えば
Three! If our eyes meet
Fall
止められない
I can't stop
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋 この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah! With this love, with this passion
MELT MELT とけちゃうよ
Melt melt, I'm melting away!
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて My darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling
届け！大好き！
Reach you! I love you!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム さあ叫びましょ
I, Love, Scream! Let's scream it out!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！ OK!
Scream! Ice Cream! OK!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム さあ叫びましょ
I, Love, Scream! Let's scream it out!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice Cream!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント
Chocomint
よりもあ・な・た！
More than that, Y-O-U!
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
アイリスちゃん！
IRyS-chan!
はーい！
Yeees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりもあ・な・た
Rather than strawberry flavor, I'd choose... Y-O-U!
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
はーい！
Yeees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりもあ・な・た
Rather than Cookie & Cream, I'd choose... Y-O-U!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yeees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き
Of course, we love...
アイ、スクリーム！
Ai, Scream!
止められない
Unstoppable!
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, with this affection!
Melt melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt!
ねぇねぇねぇ 気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
届け！大好き！
Reach them! My love!
アイ愛、スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai, Scream, Scream, let's scream it out!
スクリーム！ アイ
Scream! Ai...
アイスクリーム OK!
Ice cream! OK!
アイ愛、スクリーム スクリーム 叫びましょ
Ai, Scream, Scream, let's scream it out!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
おねがい見つけて my darling
Please find me, my darling...
慰めさせてベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, best friend, with the talent of love.
泣いてくれるかい きみのツライ 抱き締めたい ねえいいでしょう
Will you cry for me? I want to hug your pain, hey, is that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだってば
I want to share it and overcome it, I tell you.
だっだってば WAH
I-I tell you, WAH!
お願い きみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばして
Please, I want you, laugh it off...
ホップステップジャンプ さあいこうぜ
hop, step, jump, let's go!
分けてくれるかい きみに重い 暗い思い 除きたい
Will you share with me your heavy, dark thoughts? I want to remove them.
吸い取って 救いたいんだってば だっだってば
I want to absorb it and save you, I-I tell you.
ねえ あたし 知ってるよ きみがひとり 涙してるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're crying all alone, I know it.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラ？いいんじゃない？
You're down in the dumps, sobbing, is singing solo to vent okay?
ずっと一緒 もっと泣いたって
Together forever, even if you cry more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept it no matter how many times.
もう我慢しないで出してってば
Don't hold back anymore, let it out, I tell you.
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Beat beat baby
Music gets you crazy
Shock me tonight
Go beat crazy!
Fun fun baby
Dancin' feelin' hazy
Shake out of sight
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Boom boom baby
Come and shake your booty
Dig it tonight
Go beat crazy!
Go go baby
Show me that you're ready
Get satisfied
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Beat beat baby
Fun fun baby
Go beat crazy!
Boom boom baby
Go go baby
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Keep on movin' your body round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
GO BEAT CRAZY!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go, go
GO BEAT CRAZY!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
GO BEAT CRAZY!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go, go
GO BEAT CRAZY!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
GO BEAT CRAZY!
Are you ready?
カリスマックス カリスマックス
Charismax, Charismax!
Everybody make some noise!
誰も真似できやしないな
No one can ever imitate me
Starのguidance...
Star's guidance...
カリスマ
Charisma!
バズりまくり ah
Going completely viral, ah
常にtacticalに
Always acting tactically
カリスマ
Charisma!
Haterたちにご提案ディスるより
Here's a proposal for the haters: instead of dissing,
Do what you love
カリスマ
Charisma!
朝から晩まで ring a ring a ling
From morning till night, ring a ring a ling
勝ちや負け気にするの論外
Caring about winning or losing is out of the question
「ミスるの」問題
Saying "making mistakes is a problem"
とか言ってんのが大問題
is the biggest problem of all
Alright自分が正解
Alright, I am the correct answer
Everyone必ず信念を貫く
Everyone, carry through with your beliefs
We are! We are! No.1
Charismax!
最強のマインド Charismax
The strongest mind, Charismax!
時代塗り替える Charismax
Rewriting the era, Charismax!
世界が驚く
The world will be astonished
どいつもこいつも crazy, crazy man
Every single one of them is a crazy, crazy man
Charismax!
Crazy, crazy man!
常識壊してゆく Charismax
Breaking down common sense, Charismax!
まるで人生はstageみたいだ
It's as if life is a stage
皆が役者
Everyone is an actor
カリスマ
Charisma!
何でもできる そう君は何でもできる
You can do anything, yes, you can do anything
カリスマ
Charisma!
Wannabeたちにご提案今すぐに
Here's a proposal for the wannabes: right now,
Do what you want
カリスマ
Charisma!
世界に響かす ding a ding a ling
Making it resonate around the world, ding a ding a ling
空気は読むより変えてくstyle
My style is to change the vibe rather than read the room
はみ出す天才
An outstanding genius
てか愛想笑いなんてしない
I mean, I don't even fake-smile
Alright 答えは明快
Alright, the answer is clear
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone, carry through with your beliefs
We are! We are! No.1
Charismax!
才能解き放つ Charismax
Unleashing talent, Charismax!
進化をし続ける Charismax
Continuing to evolve, Charismax!
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond the limits
どいつもこいつも crazy, crazy woman
Every single one of them is a crazy, crazy woman
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone, carry through with your beliefs
We are! We are!
No.1
Charismax!
最強のマインド Charismax
The strongest mind, Charismax!
時代塗り替える Charismax
Rewriting the era, Charismax!
世界が驚く
The world will be astonished
どいつもこいつも crazy, crazy man
Every single one of them is a crazy, crazy man
Charismax!
才能解き放つ Charismax
Unleashing talent, Charismax!
進化をし続ける Charismax
Continuing to evolve, Charismax!
限界超えてゆく
Going beyond the limits
どいつもこいつも crazy, crazy woman
Every single one of them is a crazy, crazy woman
Crazy, crazy man!
常識壊してゆく Charismax
Breaking down common sense, Charismax!
[Visual: Please wait...]
Yeah!
Ah, ah...
Can I get it, get it, get all your attention?
I bet you don't know me yet.
君の奥底まで
To your very depths,
穿つ目線で
with a piercing gaze.
溢れる様
Overflowing...
IQ ammo...
獲る天下
I'll conquer the world.
A catalyst, I know, when I say go.
Put your hands up!
混沌の最中に
In the midst of chaos,
降臨した女神
the goddess has descended.
I feel it up, got it ice-cold on my body.
You wanna know, but you don't.
震撼させるイノ
An innovation that shakes the world.
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine.
Can't stop 煌めく my fantasy,
Can't stop my sparkling fantasy,
now you see.
星空を
Drinking in...
飲み染まるんだ私に
...and being dyed in the starry sky.
Hidden deep within my universe,
come find me now.
Hear the voice that's calling out.
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を
The essence of a world yet unseen...
見せてあげるから
...I will show it to you.
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus.
Under my spell, like hypnosis.
So don't get too close when I'm...
(Come-a, come-a, coming through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down, yes.
I tell you what to do,
I got nothing to prove.
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do,
脳髄まで bulletproof,
bulletproof to the core of my brain.
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus.
Back at my best, I finesse.
私の脳裏に潜む
Lurking in my mind...
怪物は no secret.
...the monster is no secret.
冷静に cool, my attitude.
Calm and cool, that's my attitude.
Target in my sight, locked in,
ready to shoot, like...
Mayday, this is an emergency.
Working under pressure, baby,
I can do this in my sleep.
世の理だって
Even the laws of this world...
書き換えてしまうような頭脳
...are rewritten by a brain like this.
When I go, when I go,
I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine.
Can't stop 煌めく my fantasy,
Can't stop my sparkling fantasy,
now you see.
銀河を
So as to...
音色で轟かすように
...make the galaxy echo with my melody.
Hidden deep within my universe,
come find me now.
Clear my mind of all these doubts.
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を
The essence of a world yet unseen...
この目で見ていたいから
...I want to see it with my own eyes.
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus.
Under my spell, like hypnosis.
So don't get too close when I'm...
(Come-a, come-a, coming through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down, yes.
I tell you what to do,
I got nothing to prove.
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do,
脳髄まで bulletproof,
bulletproof to the core of my brain.
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohn...
垂れろ頭, don't break my focus.
Bow down your heads, don't break my focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma...
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind.
I'mma get you talkin' bout it loud.
Can't get rid of me now.
唯一無二, so I'm crowned.
Peerless, so I'm crowned.
Put my feet on the ground.
巻きさらってくわ
I'm going to sweep you away.
Ace, piece of cake, it's no stress.
銀河中を魅了して what's next?
Charming the entire galaxy, what's next?
Take a guess, yes.
I tell you what to do,
I got nothing to prove.
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do,
脳髄まで bulletproof,
bulletproof to the core of my brain.
Cold when I do, what I do, when I focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohn...
垂れろ頭, don't break my focus.
Bow down your heads, don't break my focus.
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma...
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind.
Focus.
DARK ARIA
The time has come...
...to pack away...
...all the joys.
You don't wanna hear my apology.
Get it off my chest.
I would do my best.
I know what you fear,
similarities we possess.
Never will I pass the test.
The scene is fading.
Can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me,
Be the change I couldn't be.
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales?
Far from this tragedy.
Sad you had to wait for me.
Feels like an eternity.
Please forgive me for my sins.
Angels wings lifting and setting me free.
Death is gonna come for me,
Be the change I couldn't be.
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales?
Far from this tragedy.
Sad you had to wait for me.
Feels like an eternity.
Please forgive me for my sins.
Angels wings lifting and setting me free.
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
Woo! Oh, we're getting towards the end of the live.
There were so many beautiful songs, and so many beautiful guests!
I love the glasses, the Karismax and Dicey glasses. Good stuff.
Woo! And we're getting to the end, which means announcements! Yeah!
But first off, before this live—I mean, after this live, there will be a members-only party as well! So, join the RyS-fam today!
えっと、この後もね、あの、メン限パートもあるので、ぜひ...
Also, after this, there's going to be a members-only part, so please...
メンバーに、メンバーシップに入ってこい！イェーイ！
...join the member—join the membership! Yay!
歌、歌うんで。Yes.
Because I'll be singing. Yes.
Okay then, are you guys ready for the announcement?
すっごく、すっごく嬉しい告知があります！
There is a very, very happy announcement!
There's a big, big announcement I'm really, really happy about, and I can't wait! I'm super happy I get to share it with you guys!
はい、嬉しい告知いきます！まずは、こちらをご覧ください。
Alright, here comes the happy announcement! First, please look at this.
Please watch this short video!
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes / 願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
It would be you / それは、あなた。
It would be you
Oct 6th
JAPAN
TOKYO
IRyS 1st Concert
VENUE: SGC HALL ARIAKE
I will gift you with / そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
I will gift you with
Hope made of miracles / 奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
Hope made of miracles
ということで！
And so...
Yes, IRyS, I will be having my very first solo live!
in Tokyo, Japan!
IRySの、なんと、初めてのソロライブ、日本で開催されることが決定しました！ウフフ！
IRyS will be having her first ever solo live, and it's decided to be held in Japan! Woohoo!
Yes! It will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake!
えっと、場所は東京の、SGCホール有明でございます！
And the venue is SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
日程は10月6日！
The date is October 6th!
It's going to be on a Tuesday, はい、火曜日でございますね。
It's going to be on a Tuesday, yes, a Tuesday.
It'll be happening on October 6th, Tuesday, yeah!
Mark your calendars! カレンダーに書いておくれや！
Mark your calendars! Write it down on your calendars!
ずっとね、本当に夢に見ていたステージに立てることを、すごく嬉しく思いさし、思います！
I'm extremely, extremely happy that I get to stand on the stage I've dreamed of for so long!
本当に、みんなの応援のおかげです、ありがとうございます！
It is truly thanks to everyone's support, thank you so much!
It's all thanks to you guys' support that I get to have this opportunity, so thank you so much for all your support until now!
がんばるぞ！イェーイ！
I'll do my best! Yay!
えっとね、I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one.
Um, I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one.
So please look forward to it. Make sure you definitely come! If you don't come, I'll be sad. If you don't come, you'll also regret it, yes.
あの、ライブに向けて、準備めちゃくちゃ頑張ってるんで、素晴らしいライブになるように頑張ってるんで、ぜひ会場へ見に来てください！
Um, I'm working incredibly hard preparing for this live, doing my best to make it an amazing live, so please definitely come to see it at the venue!
イェーイ、見に行かないと、IRyS悲しいし、みんなも後悔するぞ！
Yay! If you don't come, IRyS will be sad and you guys will regret it!
はい！
Alright!
そして！And, along with it...
And, along with it...
Yes, I will also be releasing my very first full album! Woohoo!
なんと、IRyS、初のフルアルバム、出ます！
What's more, IRyS's first full album is coming out!
そう、なんだかんだ言ってね、今まではEPだったんですけど、フルアルバムは初めてです！
Yeah, despite everything, I've only released EPs until now, so a full album is a first!
Yeah, I've released EPs in the past, but this is the very first full album, so...
...look forward to it. There's a lot of songs.
The album jacket...
...is by Kito Koruta-sensei, very cute!
The album title is called DANGERyS, yes.
何でも「RyS」をつければいいってもんじゃないかもしれないけど、ちょうどはまったんでね、「DANGERyS」な...
It might not be that you can just add "RyS" to everything, but it fit perfectly, so "DANGERyS"...
...とても危険的でホットなアルバムになってます！Yes.
...is a very dangerous and hot album! Yes.
えっと、It is written by... I mean, there's many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world.
Um, there's many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world.
And there's going to be a lot of Eurobeat songs, but also songs that are not Eurobeat as well, new genres as well!
So, I hope you guys look forward to that.
ね、あの、国内外の様々なクリエイターに
I've also had various creators from Japan and abroad...
ユーロビート以外の楽曲も多数作ってもらってます。
...create many songs in genres other than Eurobeat.
A lot of new songs!
And I will be performing, of course, performing one of the songs for you today!
今日もね、あの、一曲披露しようかなと思ってます。
I'm planning to perform one of them for you today.
A showcase, yay!
The song I'll be showcasing for you today was written and arranged by...
...the Eurobeat circle SOUND HOLIC-san! Woohoo!
Yes, they're very famous for Eurobeat, so I'm really glad, I'm really happy to be able to work with them. Thank you so much.
えっとね、今回お披露目する楽曲は、
So, the song I'm debuting today...
作曲・編曲、国内のユーロビートを得意とするクリエイターさん、
...is composed and arranged by creators who specialize in domestic Eurobeat,
SOUND HOLICさんでございます！ありがとうございます！
SOUND HOLIC! Thank you so much!
新たなユーロビートの見せ方になると思うんで、楽しみにしてて。
I think it shows a new way of presenting Eurobeat, so look forward to it.
It's Eurobeat, but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat, so I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it.
Yes, the digital release will be happening on...
...12:00 AM JST, the upcoming 12:00 AM JST after this. So, make sure you're streaming on Spotify and other streaming services, yeah!
このあとね、えっと、デジタルリリースも各配信サイトで行われます。
After this, it will be digitally released on various streaming platforms.
えっと、0時に配信されます。
It will be released at midnight.
楽しみにしててね！
Please look forward to it!
すごくド派手な曲です。楽しみだ。
It's a super flashy song. I'm excited!
And as for the details of the album, I will be talking about that at the very end of this live, so be sure to stick till the end!
アルバムの詳細は、このあと最後の方でね、
As for the album details, near the end...
えっと、色々説明しちゃうんで、最後まで見てね。
...I will explain various things, so make sure to watch until the end!
All right then, please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME!
新しい曲聴いてください、BE MY FLAME!
Please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME!
Blazin' fire
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
(Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop)
(Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot, it's your fault, baby)
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart going up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
(Come on and come on, I wanna confess, baby, oh baby, I'm gettin' obsessed)
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
(Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, gonna be, wanna be ready for more)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazin' fire
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm baring my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play, a dangerous game
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
(Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash, breakin' me, shakin' me, makin' me crash)
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
(Drivin' me, drivin' me, drivin' me crazy, tellin' me, tellin' me what do you mean)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
I'm only getting started...
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream,
Wild desire fueling my delusion,
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
So, how did you guys like my Birthday 3D Live?
We had so much going on from the new 3D outfit debut,
new merch, to my first album announcement,
solo live announcement,
and new song performances!
I think it was packed with so much, so
I'd like to give you guys a recap and share the details.
ライブ本編どうでしたか？
How did you guys like the main live performance?
色々ね、告知盛りだくさんだったと思うので、
Since there were so many announcements,
改めておさらいと詳細をお伝えします。
I'd like to go over them again and share the details.
まずはグッズから！ First up, the merch!
First up, the merchandise! First up, the merch!
We have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS, illustrated by Inunopiske-sensei,
the ChibiRyS Tote Bag, illustrated by Lien-sensei,
the Race QueenRyS Keychain, which is a really cute Race Queen plushie keychain,
and the YabaiRyS Pouch.
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes a postcard with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped autograph.
The standard version includes a postcard with both a foil-stamped message and autograph.
And sales will start at 1:15 PM, which is like real soon if not maybe even now.
フルセットを買っていただいた方には、数量限定版は直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードが付いてきます。
For those who purchase the full set, the limited edition includes a postcard with a handwritten message and a foil-stamped copy of my autograph.
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになります。
The standard version will include a postcard with a foil-stamped copy of my autograph and message.
この後1時15分にカートオープンするよ！もうすぐだよね。
The cart opens after this at 1:15 PM! That's really soon.
続いてアルバムです。Next up, the album!
Next up is the album. Next up, the album!
This time, it's being released in two formats: the CD and vinyl! Woohoo!
Pre-orders will begin also at 1:15 PM JST at the Hololive Production Official Shop, like real soon.
As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th.
今回はCDとレコードの2種類のリリースとなっておりまして、
This time, it will be released in two formats, CD and vinyl,
この後1時15分よりホロライブオフィシャルショップにて予約が開始されます。
and pre-orders will begin after this at 1:15 PM JST at the Hololive Official Shop.
デジタルリリースは7月12日です。
The digital release will be on July 12th.
CDにはここでしか聴けない「Gravity」のリアレンジバージョンとステッカー2種類、
The CD comes with a re-arranged version of 'Gravity' that you can only hear here, and two types of stickers.
レコードにはジャケットとアナザージャケットが印刷されたLPサイズ両面ポストカードが付いてきます。
The vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized postcard with the cover jacket and alternate jacket printed on it.
ポストカードじゃないよ、ポスターカード。もっとデカいです。
It's not a postcard, it's a poster card. It's much bigger.
さらに、こちらのポスターカードには、両面のどちらかに必ず直筆サインが入ります！
Furthermore, one of the sides of this poster card will definitely be autographed by hand!
サインされる面はランダムでございます。裏面かもしれないし、表面かもしれません。
The signed side is random. It could be on the back, or the front.
The CD will include an exclusive re-arranged version of Gravity and two types of stickers,
while the vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized poster card.
Yes, a pretty darn big poster card featuring both the main and alternate album covers.
Plus, yes a big plus, one side of this poster card will definitely feature a hand-written autograph!
The signed side will be random, so it could be on either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover.
We'll see when you get it!
And BE MY FLAME, which was performed in today's 3D Live, will also be digitally released at midnight today, so don't forget to check it out.
そしてライブでお披露目した『BE MY FLAME』は、24時にデジタルリリースもあるので、忘れずにチェックしてね！
And 'BE MY FLAME', which was revealed in the live concert, will also be digitally released at midnight, so make sure to check it out!
And there's more! That's right!
My first solo live concert! Woohoo!
The venue will be...
Tokyo at SGC Hall Ariake, woo!
And it will be held on a Tuesday on October 6th.
I'm super, super, super excited for this, and I'm so glad I've got to finally announce it!
So I hope you guys will be really excited for it as well, yay!
あとね、えっとソロライブも決まりました！
Also, my solo concert has been decided!
場所は東京、SGCホール有明でございます。
The venue is Tokyo, SGC Hall Ariake.
えーっと、開催される日程は10月6日火曜日です。
And the date of the event is Tuesday, October 6th.
すっごく楽しみにしてるし、
I'm really looking forward to it,
もうとにかく、もうこんなライブがやれる機会自体が本当に、
and honestly, an opportunity to perform a concert like this...
まさかできると思ってなくて、
I never thought it would actually be possible,
とってもワクワクしてますし、これからも準備頑張ります！
so I'm super excited and will do my best preparing for it from now on!
Please look forward to further details and information in the future!
Last but not least, there will be a members-only part starting at 1:30 PM pretty soon,
so please come check it out if you can and join the family.
最後に、メンバー限定パートが1時半から始まるので、
Lastly, the members-only part starts at 1:30,
よかったらメンバーに入って見に来てね！
so if you'd like, please join the membership and come watch!
では、ありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you so much!
Thank you very much! Bye for now! Until the members' part!